{"sid": "YMZO6I283HNR_main", "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 387421, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 387421, "question": "4+3+6+13", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 392327]], "time_left_end": "296", "answered_time": 392327, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "296", "question_time_start": 392328, "question": "78+37+23+47", "correct_answer": 185, "events": [["submit", 407623]], "time_left_end": "280", "answered_time": 407623, "user_answer": "185", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "280", "question_time_start": 407623, "question": "7+68+83", "correct_answer": 158, "events": [["calc_6", 412950], ["calc_8", 413421], ["calc_+", 413849], ["calc_8", 414378], ["calc_3", 414862], ["calc_+", 415278], ["calc_7", 415773], ["calc_=", 416295], ["submit", 419071]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "269", "answered_time": 419071, "user_answer": "158", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "269", "question_time_start": 419071, "question": "8+98+77", "correct_answer": 183, "events": [["submit", 429063]], "time_left_end": "259", "answered_time": 429063, "user_answer": "183", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "259", "question_time_start": 429064, "question": "34+873", "correct_answer": 907, "events": [["submit", 435258]], "time_left_end": "253", "answered_time": 435258, "user_answer": "907", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "253", "question_time_start": 435258, "question": "63+13", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 438935]], "time_left_end": "249", "answered_time": 438935, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "249", "question_time_start": 438935, "question": "4+24+17", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 446816]], "time_left_end": "241", "answered_time": 446816, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "241", "question_time_start": 446816, "question": "24+516", "correct_answer": 540, "events": [["submit", 451968]], "time_left_end": "236", "answered_time": 451968, "user_answer": "540", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "236", "question_time_start": 451968, "question": "6+7+7+43", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 456343]], "time_left_end": "232", "answered_time": 456343, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "232", "question_time_start": 456343, "question": "53+97", "correct_answer": 150, "events": [["submit", 461192]], "time_left_end": "227", "answered_time": 461192, "user_answer": "150", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 461192, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "227", "question_time_start": 461192, "question": "8+16+28", "correct_answer": 52, "events": [["submit", 472616]], "time_left_end": "215", "answered_time": 472616, "user_answer": "52", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "215", "question_time_start": 472616, "question": "9+6+7+96", "correct_answer": 118, "events": [["submit", 480975]], "time_left_end": "207", "answered_time": 480975, "user_answer": "128", "user_correct": "False", "score": "10"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "207", "question_time_start": 480975, "question": "44+67", "correct_answer": 111, "events": [["submit", 485319]], "time_left_end": "203", "answered_time": 485319, "user_answer": "111", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "203", "question_time_start": 485319, "question": "9+83+23", "correct_answer": 115, "events": [["submit", 490919]], "time_left_end": "197", "answered_time": 490919, "user_answer": "115", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "197", "question_time_start": 490919, "question": "36+623", "correct_answer": 659, "events": [["submit", 497831]], "time_left_end": "190", "answered_time": 497831, "user_answer": "659", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "190", "question_time_start": 497831, "question": "58+496", "correct_answer": 554, "events": [["submit", 504041]], "time_left_end": "184", "answered_time": 504041, "user_answer": "552", "user_correct": "False", "score": "12"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "184", "question_time_start": 504041, "question": "9+56+17", "correct_answer": 82, "events": [["submit", 519975]], "time_left_end": "168", "answered_time": 519975, "user_answer": "62", "user_correct": "False", "score": "11"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "168", "question_time_start": 519975, "question": "9+9+3+93", "correct_answer": 114, "events": [["submit", 535423]], "time_left_end": "152", "answered_time": 535423, "user_answer": "114", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "152", "question_time_start": 535423, "question": "77+57+54+87", "correct_answer": 275, "events": [["submit", 558239]], "time_left_end": "130", "answered_time": 558239, "user_answer": "275", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "130", "question_time_start": 558239, "question": "19+89", "correct_answer": 108, "events": [["submit", 566136]], "time_left_end": "122", "answered_time": 566136, "user_answer": "108", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 566136, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "122", "question_time_start": 566136, "question": "3+48+38", "correct_answer": 89, "events": [["submit", 575095]], "time_left_end": "113", "answered_time": 575095, "user_answer": "89", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "113", "question_time_start": 575095, "question": "23+56+54+63", "correct_answer": 196, "events": [["submit", 586767]], "time_left_end": "101", "answered_time": 586767, "user_answer": "196", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "101", "question_time_start": 586768, "question": "7+38+53", "correct_answer": 98, "events": [["submit", 592607]], "time_left_end": "95", "answered_time": 592607, "user_answer": "98", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "95", "question_time_start": 592607, "question": "7+6+9+98", "correct_answer": 120, "events": [["submit", 602671]], "time_left_end": "85", "answered_time": 602671, "user_answer": "120", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "85", "question_time_start": 602671, "question": "4+17+69", "correct_answer": 90, "events": [["submit", 610585]], "time_left_end": "77", "answered_time": 610585, "user_answer": "90", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "77", "question_time_start": 610585, "question": "96+859", "correct_answer": 955, "events": [["submit", 623680]], "time_left_end": "64", "answered_time": 623680, "user_answer": "955", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "64", "question_time_start": 623680, "question": "86+759", "correct_answer": 845, "events": [["submit", 636170]], "time_left_end": "52", "answered_time": 636170, "user_answer": "845", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "52", "question_time_start": 636170, "question": "57+36", "correct_answer": 93, "events": [["submit", 642872]], "time_left_end": "45", "answered_time": 642872, "user_answer": "93", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "45", "question_time_start": 642872, "question": "7+8+7+44", "correct_answer": 66, "events": [["submit", 649480]], "time_left_end": "38", "answered_time": 649480, "user_answer": "66", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "38", "question_time_start": 649481, "question": "66+99", "correct_answer": 165, "events": [["submit", 656847]], "time_left_end": "31", "answered_time": 656847, "user_answer": "165", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 656847, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "31", "question_time_start": 656847, "question": "9+54+58", "correct_answer": 121, "events": [["submit", 663674]], "time_left_end": "24", "answered_time": 663674, "user_answer": "121", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "24", "question_time_start": 663674, "question": "8+77+56", "correct_answer": 141, "events": [["submit", 671055]], "time_left_end": "17", "answered_time": 671055, "user_answer": "141", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "17", "question_time_start": 671055, "question": "6+9+8+74", "correct_answer": 97, "events": [["submit", 679727]], "time_left_end": "8", "answered_time": 679727, "user_answer": "97", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "8", "question_time_start": 679727, "question": "8+6+7+18", "correct_answer": 39, "events": []}}}}}